[{"answer": "Oh, really? Like what", "docId": "Major-League.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I was thinking of my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Naw, I'm just not sure I'd be happy in a big organization like that. Owners are always on your back, tryin' to", "docId": "Major-League.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Down here baseball's a game, not a business. I don't wanta be a babysitter for a buncha millionaires who think they know it all already", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Well then, bonus babies or whatever you got..", "docId": "Major-League.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Don't you have any proven major league talent", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "What are you doin' there, my friend", "docId": "Major-League.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "So are mine. Is somethin' goin' around", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Everybody laughs at the Indians now, but there were other times. Even won the Series in '48. Then my friend made that catch on my friend in the '54 Series and that place's never been the same since", "docId": "Major-League.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "If we ever lost the Indians, that place would die", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I was wonderin' why you'd give an old friend a bum phone number", "docId": "Major-League.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I don't wanna talk in your office", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I don't remember you makin' any date", "docId": "Major-League.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Ancient history, my friend. I gotta look out for myself now. I don't have to be a slave to no .235 hitter", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Look, my friend, I'm sorry I followed you home but I wanna..", "docId": "Major-League.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Whose place is it", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I'm told that baseball players make very good salaries these days", "docId": "Major-League.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "How good are you", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Mine. You follow me again", "docId": "Major-League.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I just wanted to see you play", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Goin' uptown, huh", "docId": "Major-League.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You think I can't lead a regular life", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Naw, I'm not into Song of that place", "docId": "Major-League.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "my friend, that sounds pretty good. That's a detective story, right", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Someday we'll figure out how to beat those guys", "docId": "Major-League.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Sixty and sixt", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I'm, ah, a ball player", "docId": "Major-League.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Why did you come over then", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Where you goin'", "docId": "Major-League.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I didn't even get your name", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I didn't even get your name", "docId": "Major-League.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " my friend", "qsentId": 32}]